Thank you. Good Morning!
You may be seated, thank you!
Hallelujah!
Glory be to God.
I'm here to give you just a short word of exhortation.
You know God is working out the answer.
You remember the message given to you concerning reporting which is very important
and I know you are doing what the Word says.
It's an issue that will really help you in your domestic affairs, your company
and everywhere you find yourself.
The Bible says salvation is of confession and believing
so you must know that reporting should be an expression of believing.
Reporting should be an expression of believing.
Wherever you find yourself as a Christian, you are to report what you see.
As a Christian, wherever you find yourself, you are to report what you see and hear.
When you report what you see and what you hear, it settles issues, it answers questions,
it clarifies doubts and provides a way forward.
Work alone cannot help any establishment grow.
Every establishment expects two things from you: working and reporting.
I can't hear you.
[Working and reporting.]
Today you are here in the church.
You are to report whatever you see that is wrong among the workers and the members.
Don't just leave.
"No, no. Look at the way the woman behaved."
You know when we were in the church, the woman was disturbing.
Discussing this at home is a sin.
You have to report it in church; you have to write it down and give it to the usher,
"Please, I'm giving you this. Make sure you submit it to the authority".
You have to be vigilant of what is going on.
"Look at that woman. From this group to another group.
Look at her moving around. Why is she talking like that? See the way she moves!"
"See the way he passes a note! A worker!"
You have to report.
Hallelujah.
That is very important.
Reporting should be an expression of believing.
Unruly behaviours.
Not only that: the visions you have about your establishment, dreams.
There are many visions and dreams you often have.
God will show you.
You have to send a letter or a mail.
You can even because of that travel from your country to another country -
just because of that vision because you are a believer.
Hallelujah!
I'm thanking you for your prayer because God has spoken, regardless of our situations.
Rise up for prayer.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
If you honestly examine your heart in the light of God's Word,
you will discover that there is a spirit of unforgiveness, a spirit of anger,
a spirit of bitterness, a spirit of jealousy, a spirit of envy
and such a spirit break our communion with God, our relationship with God.
It opens the door to whatever situation you are in now.
You say, "I have sickness".
What is the route of sickness? Unforgiveness.
Hardship - what is the route of hardship? Envy, jealousy and anger.
That is the route, the road to get to you.
Nightmare, barrenness, anger, jealousy, unforgiveness, bitterness - these are routes.
You will see many people you have put in the prison yard and you are still walking everywhere.
You will see people that are in bondage just because of you.
Are you talking of divorce?
Many men you have divorced; many women you have divorced.
You say, "Over your life, the woman will not see the children!"
What is your problem?
Why will the woman not see her children; why will the man not see his children?
You have divorced him or her.
And you are calling, "God, God!" - for what?
The SCOAN Sunday Service
You people have divorced.
You say, "The man will not see the children again!"
and you are trying to keep these children away from the man or the woman.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
"Father, forgive them" - both accused and accuser.
"Father, forgive them" - both wrong and right.
You say it is witchcraft, they bewitched you, they attacked you.
Who attacked you?
When you are carrying an unforgiving spirit, envy and jealousy, you say they attacked you.
You don't need to be attacked; once you have that spirit, you have attacked yourself.
Are you there?
Listen to me again.
It opens the door to whatever challenges you are in.
Are you sick, facing hardship, poverty, loneliness, rejection?
Whatever you are facing, the route of those things is unforgiveness, envy, jealousy, bitterness.
These are the routes.
You don't need the enemy to attack you; once you have these, you have attacked yourself.
Once the relationship is broken, what else again?
You are accessible to satan.
It breaks the communion; it breaks the relationship.
These are the things that break the relationship.
Once your relationship breaks with God, what else again? You are on your own.
Unforgiveness, envy, jealousy, bitterness, strife and hatred
open the door to whatever you are in.
When you leave here now, it is not too late.
Just from your heart, you can say, "Yes, what this man says, I am ready".
Once you say you are ready and you concur in your heart, the job is done.
When you leave here, you can continue to reconcile, send a test message,
a phone call and try to settle yourself.
I release you from the pain of the past.
I release you from the unforgiving spirit, that bitterness, envy, jealousy.
Be released, in the name of Jesus!
You know you can be released.
You know that?
Be released, in the name of Jesus!
Such spirits break the communion, relationship with God.
Once it breaks, you are on your own.
Once you are on your own, here is poverty; here is affliction.
Once you are on your own, here is hardship.
Once you are on your own, here is rejection.
Once you are on your own, here is nightmare.
With a pure heart, man knows that Jesus saves.
With a pure heart, man knows that Jesus saves, heals, blesses and delivers.
You say, "I am healed!" You are about to lose that healing with that unforgiving spirit.
You are about to lose that deliverance with that unforgiving spirit,
with bitterness, envy and jealousy in your heart.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
You can receive deliverance but with an unforgiving spirit, you will lose it.
With that unforgiving spirit, envy and jealousy in your heart, that cannot be permanent.
This is why our life is epileptic.
It goes this way; later down.
This way - down.
And you keep asking yourself why all this is not with you forever.
It can be forever.
You are healed forever; you are blessed forever.
It is a paste-tense victory but because of an unforgiving spirit,
envy, jealousy, bitterness and hatred in you, that cannot be permanent.
As you are standing, begin to examine yourself, "What is wrong?
What is the next thing now?"
It is better not to receive than to receive and lose it.
Ask yourself, "What is wrong with me?
Why is my life not constant?
I'm happy now - another time...
I'm blessed - another time...
Why?"
Jesus is the same yesterday, today and forever.
His blessing is the same yesterday, today and forever.
His healing is the same yesterday, today and forever.
"Why all this?"
"Why?"
How can you labour, sweat and suddenly you are back to square one again?
MESSAGE TITLE: BELIEVE AND CONFESS | PART 3
You are here today because you see the strength of God - from strength to strength.
That is why you are here - irrespective of tribulation, persecution, hatred.
Strength to strength - that is why you are here, irrespective of name-calling.
When you expect something to spoil and it is not spoiled, you will join them.
When you expect something to destroy and it refuses to destroy, you will join them.
When you expect something to disappear and it refuses to disappear, you will join them.
That is why you are here today.
Honestly examine your heart; Christianity lies in the heart.
Tell your neighbour, "Christianity lies in the heart".
You see this appearance - it is a camouflage.
Your make-up, your hair, your beauty, you are handsome -
this appearance is a camouflage; the real man is your heart.
This is why the Bible says faith is of man's heart.
The one that worships God is your heart, not your body.
Listen again!
Honestly examine your heart in the light of God's Word, without prejudice.
Honestly examine your heart and you will find that your heart is full of an unforgiving spirit,
bitterness, envy and jealousy.
"Forgive us as we forgive others" - is that not the promise?
"Forgive us as we forgive those who sin against us."
So, why have an unforgiving spirit?
Why bitterness? Why envy? Why jealousy?
You are what God says you are. Why compare yourself to others?
Why measuring yourself with others?
Why?
"No, look, I'm too fat. I need to be slim. Look at that one - he is very slim."
You have gone to the car park; you have examined many cars there.
You say, "Ah, I see this car - I must get my own."
You would do anything to get your own.
Honestly examine your heart in the light of God's Word;
you will see a heart holding grudges, envy and jealousy.
Father, release Your children, in the name of Jesus!
Release Your children, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch The Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Every unclean spirit in your career,
every unclean spirit in your life,
every unclean spirit - leave my people, in the name of Jesus!
God has spoken - rejoice!
Rejoice!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch The Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
I cover you with the Blood of Jesus!
I seal you with the Blood of Jesus!
Be covered with the Blood of Jesus!
Begin a new life!
A new beginning!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch The Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
A new beginning is a new life,
a new direction,
a new way.
A new beginning!
A new beginning, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch The Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Someone was asking me four days ago,
"Sir, am I a real person God wants me to be?"
I asked, "What is the meaning of this grammar?
What do you mean by 'Am I a real person God wants me to be'?"
He said, "Because..." - he realised that he doesn't know how to go forward again.
He is a Christian.
"You said you are a Christian and you are saying this. This is blaspheming."
The SCOAN Sunday Service
If you want to be the person God wants you to be, if you want to know your destiny,
you need to know God better.
Get to know God better.
The way you know God - you know God by the senses, by your eyes.
"Yes, this is true."
"This is this; this is that."
By what you see, you know God; by what you hear, you know God;
by what you touch, you know God; feeling - you know God.
He was asking me, "What do I mean by knowing God better?"
I said, "You know God better - you know God by your senses".
He said, "Yes, yes".
"Ok, if you say you know God beyond your senses,
can you tell me - I'm here now - what are you looking at?"
He said, he sees T.B. Joshua, he sees my hand, my nose.
"No, no, no.
If you know people around me here, you know I'm a camouflage.
The face you are seeing is a camouflage."
To know the person God wants you to be, to know your destiny, you need to know God better.
Tell your neighbour.
[To know the person God wants you to be, to know your destiny, you need to know God better.]
I can't hear you.
You know God - no doubt.
But you need to know God better.
You say, you know God.
By senses - what you see, hear - that is how you know God.
This is carrot, this is fruit, this is this, this is that.
Beyond this carrot - you cannot see beyond.
Beyond T.B. Joshua - you cannot see.
All you see is T.B. Joshua, he is holding a mic - that's all.
You need to know God better by discovering your spiritual gifts.
The Bible says no one can say "Jesus is Lord," except by the help of the Holy Spirit.
God is Spirit and His worshippers worship Him in Spirit and truth.
How can you worship God without the Spirit of God?
How can you know your destiny without the Spirit of God?
No one can say, "Jesus is Lord," except by the help of the Holy Spirit.
Without your spiritual gift, you are zero.
Without your spiritual gift, you will continue to worship God by the senses -
what you see, what you hear, what you feel, what your emotions say, what your feelings say.
You cannot become God's person on the history and theory about the Word of God.
Tell your neighbour.
This is what makes you a child of God, a born again.
History and theory about the Word of God, that makes you - no!
You cannot become God’s person on the history and theory about the Word of God alone.
Indeed, it is valuable but alone - history and theory of the Bible -
you cannot just call your spiritual gift.
I command healing on you, in the name of Jesus!
Be healed, in the name of Jesus!
Be healed, in the name of Jesus Christ!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch The Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
God has spoken, in Jesus' name!
I can't hear you!
[Amen!]
I can sense God's healing touching you.
I can sense God's deliverance touching you, in Jesus' name!
Hear this: God has spoken!
Rejoice!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch The Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Don't forget the message for you.
The spirit of unforgiveness, anger, bitterness breaks the communion with God,
breaks relationship with God
and once that relationship is broken, you are on your own.
Those spirits - malice, bitterness, envy, jealousy, hatred, unforgiveness -
you have this in your heart within you,
it opens the door to whatever you are facing, to whatever situation you are in.
Are you facing sickness, disease, whatever - it opens the door.
You don't need enemy to attack you; you have attacked yourself.
You know what it means when Jesus says, "Forgive them as you forgive those who trespassed against you".
With a pure heart, man knows that Jesus saves, heals and delivers.
Please, with pure heart!
This is why we gave you faith bracelets.
We have prayed over this; we put it on our altar before giving it to you
- just to take you from kindergarten, baby.
Things of the Spirit, you have to start from the foundation.
You start it on the outside, to remind you on the outside that you need to reset your belief.
Each time you sit down watching football on the television or whatever, it would be in your hand.
"Take more of me and give me more of You."
You would not know when you voice out, "Jesus!", instead of "Hey!"
Because "Hey!" is much of your language.
So you have to be pregnant of Jesus to shout "Jesus!"
We manifest what we possess.
Sometimes in the dream, when your wife, husband or children sleep,
side-by-side with you, in the night she would say, "My honey!"
- "What happened?"
- "It was a nightmare."
Because she is manifesting what she possesses; she possesses honey.
Even inside the vehicle when the vehicle is about to have an accident,
you say, "Hey!" - she/he is manifesting what she/he possesses.
You have to possess Jesus to manifest Jesus.
That is all.
This will help you:
"In the name of Jesus, in the blood of Jesus..." - on the outside.
You need something to help you on the outside.
When you are alone, when you are about to sleep, you lie on the bed,
that is the last thing you would do before you sleep.
Just lie on the bed - "Jesus Christ, take more of me and give me more of You."
To flush out all this... - that is it.
You need that.
Let's pray for our nation.
Whatever you have with you as a contact, contact point.
Bless our nation, Lord.
Redeem our nation, Lord.
God's intervention!
I can't hear you.
[Amen!]
Yes, God's intervention.
It's like every nation, every country today is facing challenges.
On the last day
Only true believers shall be raptured
I can't hear you.
On the last day
Only true believers shall be raptured
God's intervention!
Open your lips and begin to rebuke challenges, corruption, misjudge, misrule.
Right now, open your lips and pray.
Misjudge, misrule, killing, stealing, destruction.
Prayer For The Nations
With Prophet T.B. Joshua
God's intervention!
In Jesus Christ's name we pray.
Right now, pray for your leaders; ask God to redeem your leaders and put them on track.
Strengthen them with wisdom and understanding;
cover them with the blood of Jesus.
Prayer For The Nations
With Prophet T.B. Joshua
In Jesus Christ's name we pray.
I can't hear you.
[Amen!]
Prayer For The Nations
With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Listen once again: God has spoken.
You may be seated. Thank you.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Hallelujah!
The issue about your heart is a fundamental issue.
You have received all the deliverance here today, all the blessing here today,
breakthrough without a pure heart.
You will lose them.
It is a pure heart that maintains the blessing of God.
It is a pure heart that maintains God's blessing.
Maintenance is very important.
I know you have been delivered but don't forget your heart.
With a pure heart, man knows that Jesus saves, man knows that Jesus heals,
man knows that Jesus blesses.
There is no way you can maintain God's blessing without a pure heart.
So, we have to be serious.
Heart - the hearts I'm seeing are full of unforgiveness,
bitterness, envy, jealousy.
How can I continue to tell you this and yet, the hurt is still there.
Envy, jealousy, bitterness, hatred, unforgiving spirit.
A lot of people I'm seeing among the crowd, sitting down
still have that unforgiving spirit.
That shows that what is not permanent is not of God.
What is not done well is not done at all.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
So in this case, will you be ready when the Lord comes?
It could be tomorrow when you are not even here; you are home.
Will the Lord meet you?
Now, I'm leaving you in faith; will I meet you tomorrow in faith?
With unforgiving spirit?
I'm leaving you now in faith; will I meet you next Sunday with unforgiving spirit?
It is not possible.
I'm leaving you now in faith, will I meet you next Sunday with bitterness in your heart?
So it is a waste.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Forget about miracle, deliverance - we are talking of soul.
You keep talking of your knowledge of the Scripture.
I know you have the knowledge but on the history, theory, about the Word of God.
That cannot save you alone.
On the history, theories, the Word of God - that cannot save you.
You can read the Bible from Genesis to Revelation, quoting from verses to verses.
But yet, on the last day, you are in hell - hell fire.
We are doing this, having the history and theory about the Word of God
for the purpose of preaching and teaching.
To preach it - "Jesus is Lord!"
And teach it as a lecturer or whatever we call it.
This is the reason why we just have the history and theory of it.
We are only made spiritual by living in the Word and by the Word living in us.
Tell your neighbour.
That's all.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Your calling and your spiritual gift are one.
You say, "What is my calling?"
Somebody says, "T.B. Joshua, what is my calling as a Christian?"
You ask me about your callling; what about your spiritual gift?
Your calling and your spiritual gift are one.
Your calling - you say, "What is my calling?"
"You are talking of your spiritual gift."
"What is my spiritual gift?"
"You are talking of your calling."
The SCOAN Sunday Service
So the whole thing is mixed up.
So, please, I want to leave you. Thank you very much.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
TT: Unknown
RV: Mel Flowers 01/04/2019